coinhills.com 2015-03-22

# Privacy Policy - Coinhills

Coinhills is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

##  Information you provide us 

We ask for certain information such as your email and username when you register for a Coinhills account, or if you correspond with us. We may also retain any messages you send through the Service, and may collect information you provide in User Content you post to the Service. 

We use this information to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of the Service. Your username and if you choose to disclose it, will be published publicly. Once published your username may not be able to be removed. 

##  Promotion and Marketing communications 

We use the information we collect or receive, such as your email address, to communicate directly with you. We may send you emails containing newsletters, promotions, and special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you will be given the option to opt out or change your preferences. 

We also use your information to send you Service-related emails (e.g., account verification, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security notices). 

##  Analytics information 

We may directly collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools and services, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user. 

##  Cookies information 

When you visit the Service, we may send one or more cookies — a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters — to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets Coinhills help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. 

A cookie may also convey information to us about how you use the Service (e.g., the pages you view, the links you click and other actions you take on the Service), and allow us or our business partners to track your usage of the Service over time. 

A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. 

A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled. Full details can be found on our Cookie Policy. 

##  Links to other Web Sites 

To give you a better service, our website can connect you with a number of links to other local and international websites. When connecting to such other websites you will no longer be subject to this policy but to the privacy policy of the new site. 

##  Transaction Security Policy 

This site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) to ensure secure transmission of your personal data. SSL applies encryption between two points such as your PC and the connecting server. Any data transmitted during the session will be encrypted and then decrypted at the receiving end. This will ascertain that data cannot be read during transmission. 

##  Controlling your personal information 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. 

##  Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Coinhills may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. 

##  Contact Us 

If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at [support@coinhills.com](mailto:support@coinhills.com)
